just like, for example, the Kazakhs made
так же как например казахи сделали
Independence and live in their own country,
Независимость и живут в своей стране
develop their language, culture, normally
развивают свой язык культуру нормально
cool, yes. They will also be from Bashkor, Tami, with the
круто да Также будут из с башкор Тами с
Tatars, with the Ingush and with everyone.
татарами с ингушами и со всеми
Hello, Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk. Where are you from? We are from Moscow,
Хмельницке Вы откуда Мы с Москвы
native Muscovites, no the Republic of
коренные москвичи нет а ской Республики
Bashkortostan  Oh, you are
Башкортостан О вы
Bashkort Yes, I understand what you’re talking about
башкорт Да понял о чём общаетесь
here Yes, just on Well, we’re just communicating in
тут Да просто на Ну просто общаемся в
Moscow, study yes Who is a
Москве учитесь да На
programmer, applied mathematics? It’s cool, what course of the second did I understand? Why exactly is she a programmer? She’s applied
именно она программист она прикладная
mathematics, let’s go? Yes, simply, I mean, why? Well,
математика пошли Да просто В смысле
why did
зачем Ну почему именно эту специальность
you choose this specialty Well?  it sounded cool and
выбрали Ну она к круто звучала а круто
applied mathematics sounded cool yes yes And you seem to be
звучала прикладная математика да да А вы
fumbling around in mathematics in
типа шарите в математике в
programming Well, yes, I understood that
программировании Ну да понял это именно
you were the one who entered some fashionable university in
вы в какой-то модный ВУЗ поступили в
Moscow, not the most And which one we don’t like
Москве не самый А какой не не любим
to say Yes, it’s dumb, I understood I just
говорить Да это стрёмно понял Я просто
know that  there is a Moscow fister there, like the
знаю что там Московский фистер есть типа
coolest one, yes But a fister is not,
самый крутой да А фистер нет
we understand, I understand, yes, it would be a bit hard
мы понял понял понял Да тяжеловато было
there, I understand And so you are like, well, applied
бы там понял А так вы типа ну прикладная
mathematics. As I understand it, you
математика Я так понял у вас там
already taught discrete mathematics there, yes
дискретная математика уже преподавала да
And there was discrete mathematics, yes, you like discrete
А дискретка была да любите дискретную
mathematics Well, not really there  The teacher
математику Ну не очень там преподаватель
was like that, he didn’t explain well, in
такой себе был он плохо объяснял на
fact, you had to look at the appearance
самом деле приходилось по видом смотреть
But yes, they read it themselves and figured it out, it
А да сами там взяли почитали разобрались
wasn’t like that. Well, we watched the video and the
не было такого Да ну по видео смотрели а
programming we already went through, well, we
по программированию что проходили уже ну
had c+ Plus a little bit
у нас си был c+ Plus чуть-чуть
now we need this program  myself Yes, they
сейчас в это проге надо самому Да там
explain everything the same way, these
там всё одно и тоже объясняют вот эти
arrays there are
вот массивы там
conventional, I’m just not there, I’m a lawyer myself. I
условны я просто неша там я сам юрист Я
remember, in short, when I was at school, we
помню Короче когда был в школе ещё у нас
also had computer science, we were forced to
информатика тоже была нас там заставляли
write something with C+ Plus, and the teacher called me to the blackboard
c+ Plus что-то писать и к доске меня
and for me to explain What is the
вызвал препод и чтобы я объяснил Чем
difference between plus plus a variable and
отличается плюс плюс переменная и
vice versa, variable plus plus I
наоборот переменная плюс плюс я та и бля
haven’t [ __ ] caught up with me since childhood This question has been
не догнал Меня с детства Вот это вопрос
tormenting me Well, variable plus plus is
мучает Ну переменная плюс плюс - это
just adding units and plus plus plus
просто единиц прибавится а а плюс плюс
changes Most likely I don’t know for sure
перемен Скорее всего я не не знаю точно
there too  one is added, but there
там тоже прибавляется единица но там
it is dadada, this is the essence In general, this is the essence
это дадада это суть В общем это суть
not even in short, it turns out in memory It seems that I
даже не в короче в память получается
didn’t understand, there was a similar
Вроде да не понял вот там там была такая
task there K is equal to zero So, and after
задача же K равно нулю Так ну и после
that they write to p PS well, or there, for example,
этого пишут к п ПС ну или там например
plus plus K Here  for example, how do they
плюс плюс К Вот например чем они
differ from p PS just k will be equal to
отличаются к п ПС просто к будет равно
one and plus PC there is also equal to one
единице а плюс ПК там тоже равно единице
But there is no Look in my opinion Well, in short,
Но там нет Смотри по-моему Ну короче ты
when you make a variable in memory It has a
когда в памяти переменную делаешь У неё
cell there, let’s say 28 and it seems
есть ячейка там допустим 28 и у неё
like the cell changes to like twenty
вроде ячейка меняется типа на двадцать
ninth something like that Most likely I
девятую что-то такое Скорее всего я
don’t know exactly damn For me it’s something
точно не знаю бля Для меня это что-то
very complicated it’s well it would have been at school it
очень сложное это ну это в школе было б
wouldn’t be possible some cells [ __ ] It just
не может какие-то ячейки бля Там просто
made sense how memory works Well there well
было смыс как работает память Ну там ну
although at school it’s not clear why
хотя в школе непонятно зачем
it’s  for school purposes it’s not necessary yes I understand well yes
это для школьны не надо да Понял хорошо
you have some questions for me yes What are you doing I’m dealing with the
А вы чем занимаетесь Я занимаюсь
collapse of the Russian Federation here is a
распадом Российской Федерации вот карта
profile map by the way Yes Uh how will the
кстати профильная Да Ээ как будут
regions be divided it will be for example the
делиться регионы вот будет например
Republic of Sakha Yakutia Yes
Республика Саха Якутия Да независимая
independent Buryatia uh Siberia will be
Бурятия независимая ээ Сибирь будет
independent Yes, a separate state and
независимая Да отдельным государством и
so on Yes, by the way, your Bashkartastan
так дальше Да кстати ваш башкартастан
will also be independent
тоже будет независимы
Find what light it is on the map
Найди каким он светом на карте
so now
так сейчас
a second, well, if you are here Kazakhstan dadada,
секунду ну если вы тут Казахстан дадада
red seems to be no, it’s not red Yes, red is red, something is
вот красный кажется нет не кра Да
small Well, I don’t remember that one, I
маленький Ну вроде такой не помню
don’t  this is not Bastan no no no definitely no
то не это не Бастан не нет нет точно нет
not orange exactly what is orange
не оранжевый точно а что же оранжевый
now Let's see what's
такое сейчас Давайте посмотрим что же у
on my map now we'll compare
меня на карте такое сейчас мы сравним
let's now well there near Bashkortostan
давайте сейчас ну там у Башкортостана
This is something like this
Вот такая вот
no wait stop stop stop
примерно нет подожди стоп стоп стоп ты
don't look at how the Republic is now  We are
не смотри как Сейчас Республики Мы же
doing how it will disintegrate, you
делаем как оно будет распадаться
understand how Yes, for example, to
понимаешь как ться Да например к
annex part of the
башкортостану присоединять часть
Orenburg region and part of
Оренбургской области и часть
Chelyabin to Bashkortostan then Well then, I won’t say that
челябин тогда Ну тогда я так не скажу
because it’s like historical
потому что как это оде исторические
Bashkor lands like So how do you
башкор земли типа Так а как вы
determine Which one is now now look
определяете Какая сейчас сейчас смотри
So that’s about there
Так вот о есть
So now now now here is
Так сейчас сейчас сейчас вот
Bashkartastan, here it is,
башкартастан
here it is, here is Bashkartastan, you
бы вот оно оно вот тут башкартастан
see this little red one, Bashkartastan Yes,
видишь вот это красненькая башкартастан
and it will be joined by a
Да и к нему присоединится вот туда
corridor there called Yes, you were separated,
коридор называется Да вот Вас отделили
as it were, from the Orenburg region Lenin when he
как бы Оренбургской области Ленин когда
came up with the Russian Federation Yes, he took
придумал Российскую Федерацию Да он взял
a piece from the Bashkortos and divided you
у башкорто отобрал кусок и разделил вас
from the Kazakhs You are Turkic peoples and
от казахов Вы же тюркские народы и
related truth Uh-huh Yes, and here between
родственные правда Угу Да а тут между
you they made a strip of Russians Orenburg a
вами сделали полоску русских Оренбург
small small strip there that is 20
маленький маленькую полоску там что 20
km Yes, the width of the Orenburg region, yes
км Да ширина Оренбургская область да
If I’m not
Если я не
mistaken, this is two-sixth Yes, the Orenburg
ошибаюсь вот двад шестая Да Оренбургская
region This strip of the Orenburg
область Вот это полоска Оренбургской
region moved you away from the Kazakhs  Yes,
области вас отодвинула от казахов Да
so that you don’t have a border with them
чтобы у вас не было границы с ними вот
after the partition of the Russian Federation Yes, it is
после раздела Российской Федерации Да
planned to have one, read it, it’s
планируется есть такой почитайте
called the Kuvandyk corridor Write it down for
называется кувандыкский коридор Запишите
yourself, read it, it’s interesting what the
себе почитайте вот интересно что такое
Kuvandyk
кувандыкский
corridor is, Koa Kuvandyk
коридор коа кувандыкский
Ava Kuvandyk
ава кувандыкский
corridor How do you determine How it
коридор Как вы определяете Как как оно
will disintegrate, look at it, I’m not
будет распадаться это смотрите это не я
defining it  this is a map uh look
определяю это карта э вот смотрите
Go to the website tions RF org Yes a map
Зайдите на сайт tions RF org Да карта
uh like an organization of
э как бы организация
uh peoples in Russia yes who
ээ народов в России да которые
are going to secede from the Russian
собираются выйти из состава Российской
Federation Yes to gain independence Yes
Федерации Да обрести независимость Да
like Salovat Yulaev for example you have
вот как как Саловат Юлаев например у Вас
him brol and there or nodded here go
он брол и там или закивали вот заходите
to  this site here are
на этот сайт вот и
your leaders It wasn’t me who drew the map, yes, that
лидеры ваши Это же не я рисовал карту да
is, for example, the leaders of Bashkortostan Yes,
то есть например лидеры Башкортостана Да
for example, who now Putin
например которые вот сейчас Путин их
wants to put them there Yes, but if the Kalmyks are
хочет там посадить Да вот если калмыки
also Ingush And so on So they
также ингуши И так дальше Вот они
gathered and they held a congress on
собрались и они делали конгресс
how to live after the collapse of the Russian
как жить после распада Российской
Federation  because the Russian
Федерации потому что Российская
Federation
Федерация
should already cease to exist,
уже должна прекратить своё существование
this is the collapse of the Russian Empire,
это идёт распад Российской империи
remember the history of 1917, yes, the First
помните историю 1917 год да первая
World War was going on, there were empires there, the Austro
Мирова война идт были империи там
-Hungarian Ottoman Russian,
австро-венгерская Османская Российская
remember this happened, yes, as a result of this
помните такое было да вследствие этой
war, these empires fell apart, the
войны распались эти империи
Austro-Hungarian empire broke up into
австро-венгерская распалась на
independent Austria, Hungary there
независимые Австрию там Венгрию
Czechoslovakia And so on Yes, the Russian one
Чехословакию И так дальше Да Российская
also collapsed, Finland Ukraine
тоже распалась стала Финляндия Украина
there Poland became Independent And even the Ottoman
там Польша Независимый Да ещё Османская
Empire collapsed and then Lenin came and
империя развалилась а потом Ленин пришёл
reassembled it a little back and seized the lands
пересобрал немножко назад захватил земли
There, the Caucasus Ukraine and made the Soviet
Там Кавказ Украину и сделал Советский
Union This is how they restored a little
Союз Это как Вот восстановил немножко
part of the Russian Empire in the first
часть Российской империи в де первом
year The Soviet Union collapsed  This was the
году Советский Союз распался Это был
second stage of the collapse of the Russian Empire,
второй этап распада Российской Империи
Latvia Lithuania Estonia Ukraine
отошли Латвия Литва Эстония Украина
Belarus Kazakhstan moved away And so on now
Белорусь Казахстан И так дальше сейчас
Yes, the third stage of the collapse of the Russian
Да идёт третий этап распада Российской
Empire is underway Yes to independent
Империи Да на независимые уже
states That is, the Bashkor as a nation
государства То есть башкор как нация да
was formed and are moving towards proclamation; the
сформировалась и идут к провозглашении
Tatars as a nation were formed are moving towards the
татары как нации сформировалась идут к
proclamation; they made Independence  and
провозглашении сделали Независимость и
they live in their own country, develop their language,
живут в своей стране развивают свой язык
culture, it’s normal, cool, and it will be the same
культуру нормально круто да также будет
with the Bashkor Tami, with the Tatars, with the Ingush, and
и с башкор Тами с татарами с ингушами и
with
со
everyone it’s clear. I
всеми понятно
understand, yes, that is, we saw you in
Понял да да то есть вот видели у вас в
Bashkortostan, there were these unrest in
Башкортостане там были эти волнения в
Baymak. Well, that’s there behind Mount Shikhan  it
Баймаке Да ну это там за гору Шихан это
was the Armed Forces, yes, because Moscow wants it,
ВС было да потому что Москва хочет
Moscow takes these resources from the republics,
Москва забирает из республик вот эти
yes, and in return it doesn’t give anything in the wrong
ресурсы да А взамен ничего не отдаёт не
place, they wanted to build some kind of plant, yes, that’s right.
там какой-то завод хотели построить да
And Bashkor, why are you going to
правильно А башкор ты вы зачем будем
give it
давать
right, they killed the one who
прально подили того кто
spoke? Let’s have good luck
говори Давайте Удачно вам там
programming your escape there further
программировать побегу дальше
preach more importantly dumbfounded
проповедовать важливе оголошення
write to Tsei reserve channel Andriy
пишиться на Цей резервный канал Андрий
pok chatroulette I created another channel
пок чатрулетка я створив ще один канал
on some vikladav unique video I
на який викладав уникальни вдео я не
haven’t been on this channel or streams
були ни на цьому канали ни на стримах
write to new there every day they will
пишиться на нього там кожен день будуть
appear but also Novi video squeak comment PD
виходити но и Нови вдео писка комент ПД
every video YouTube  his effektivni
кожним вдео щоб YouTube его ефективни
prova mi pon collapsed that channel so
прова ми пон рухну той канал для того
that more people could extract information from
щоб бильше людей отримували информацию з
our videos so that this is our channel Yes, a
наших вдео тому що Цей наш канал Да
little bit of YouTube having driven your ban, we will
трошки YouTube загнав твый бан мы будем
try more in parallel to work one
пробу ще паралельно робити один
write
пиши